♪ I'll try to be a cat ♪ (According to the Literature Reading Group author monster monster if the fire novel work "today also want to be a cat" adaptation)
=Kucingku, Pacarku=
[Episode 18]
= Episode 18 =
I'm done.
Selesai.
It seems that Fu Sichen has begun to doubt it.
(Sepertinya Fu Si Chen sudah mulai curiga)
How could I possibly understand what you're talking about?
Bagaimana mungkin aku mengerti apa yang kamu katakan?
Are you kidding me?
Kamu bercanda apa?
Look at me, I'm a little cat.
Lihat, aku hanya kucing kecil.
Look at me.
Melirikku, melirikku.
I can also sharpen my claws.
Aku bisa mengasah cakar.
It's funny.
Tongkat kucing.
I love teasing cats.
Aku paling suka bermain kucing.
Look.
Kamu lihat,
I'm just an ordinary kitten.
Aku hanya kucing biasa.
Actually, I have someone I like.
Sebenarnya aku punya seseorang yang aku sukai.
I've done so much.
Aku sudah melakukan begitu banyak
Can't she understand?
Apakah dia masih tidak mengerti?
You know,
Menurutmu,
Does she like me?
Apakah dia menyukaiku?
Pei Zhen.
Pei Zhen.
Congratulations on winning the best actor award.
Selamat kamu memenangkan penghargaan aktor terbaik tahun ini.
Why haven't you shot any scenes this year?
(Kenapa tahun ini kamu tidak syuting satu film pun?)
Are you letting me go?
♪ Apakah kamu mengalah padaku? ♪
no no no
no no no
It's me.
Aku...
Has found the love of my life.
Telah menemukan cinta dalam hidupku
Decided to quit the entertainment industry.
Memutuskan untuk keluar dari industri hiburan.
Let's go.
Ayo kita pergi.
Fu Sichen, don't go.
(Fu Si Chen, kamu jangan pergi)
How can you be with this woman?
♪ Bagaimana kau bisa bersama wanita ini? ♪
Fu Sichen, come back.
(Fu Si Chen, kamu kembali)
It ticks me off
Membuatku marah.
Commander Fu.
Fu Si Chen.
You are such a pig.
Dasar kamu wanita murahan.
What happened? Did you have a nightmare?
Kenapa? Mimpi buruk?
Don't be afraid. Brother is here.
Jangan takut, Kakak ada di sini.
Pei Zhen, are you feeling better?
Pei Zhen, apakah kamu sudah membaik?
My parents are not at home.
Ayah ibuku tidak ada di rumah.
It hurts so much.
Sakit kepala sekali.
Your fever hasn't gone down yet.
Demammu belum turun.
Let me take you to the hospital.
Aku antar kamu ke rumah sakit.
No.
Tidak pergi
I'm not going to the hospital.
Aku tidak pergi ke rumah sakit.
We don't need the injection.
Kita tidak disuntik.
I promise.
Aku berjanji.
Hang in there. I'll be there soon.
Bertahanlah, sebentar lagi sampai
Commander Fu.
Fu Si Chen.
Don't be afraid, brother.
Jangan takut, Kakak ada di sini.
But in fact,
Tapi kembali lagi,
He's pretty.
Dia lumayan cantik.
Why didn't you notice it before?
Kenapa sebelumnya tidak menyadarinya?
Especially the lips.
Terutama bibirnya.
It looks soft.
Kelihatannya lembut sekali.
Pei Pei.
Pei.
Wake up.
Kamu cepat bangun.
Come back to me, okay?
Kembalilah padaku, oke?
No animals were harmed during the filming.
(Tidak ada hewan yang terluka saat syuting film ini)
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(Hak siar jaringan informasi serial kembali) [Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.] Eksklusif untuk menikmati)